<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brianna Weber</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brianna Weber</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time with Python</title>
      <link>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>I was not excited to learn python, it took me so long to finally understand are on a basic level. I was scared to switch to a second coding language.
Initially it was really difficult for me to keep basic concepts down, such that in python it starts with 0 while in R it starts with 1.
While it was difficult for me to learn python I am glad I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have been working on:
  Project 1
  Project 2
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project2</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Brianna Weber BAW2929Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting
data(&amp;quot;Salaries&amp;quot;)The dataset that I picked for this project is the ‘Salaries’ dataset within the ‘carData’ package. This dataset has 397 observations of 6 different variables. These variables are; ‘rank’,‘discipline’,‘yrs.service’, ‘yrs.since.phd’,‘sex’, and ‘salary.’The different levels of rank include Associate professor, Assistant Professor, and Professor. Discipline is broken into two categories, A, “theoretical” departments, and B, “applied” departments. Salary is based on a nine-month salary in dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project_One</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Project 1The two datasets that are going to be used are both found within the “dataset” package within R.The first dataset I chose is ‘USArrests’, this is a data set that has four varibles for each of the fifty US states, these variables are ‘Murder’, ‘Assault’, ‘UrbanPop’, and ‘Rape’. Murder, Rape, and Assualt are the number of accounts per 100,000, while UrbanPop is the percent of urban population in that state.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>